onlinemovies.pro 2012-09-19

# Name.ly » Privacy Policy

Our company respects the value of personal information that you share with us. As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from visitors to the web site, other than when voluntarily submitted. We will only use submitted information to improve your blogging experience.

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. We will only use your personal information lawfully (in accordance with the [Data Protection Act 1998](http://name.ly/dataprotectionact1998/)).

Reason we may collect personal information are as follows:

  * In order that we provide you with better services, more efficiently and accurately
  * To dissuade fraudulent users of our web site(s)

We do not sell or disclose any information regarding your details to other companies or mailing lists.

In accordance with the [Privacy and Electronic Communications Act](http://name.ly/dataprotectionact1998/) we do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses.

We or related partner companies will not email you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

The type of information we will collect about you may include: Name, Address, Phone Number, Mobile Number, Email Address, IP Address (to help verify the authenticity of an order), Credit/Debit Card Details (we store only partial data).

We will never collect personally identifiable information about you without your explicit consent.

You can check your account information online by logging in to your account. If you find any inaccuracies please amend them where possible or inform us via email. Please note we archive information relating to orders at the point of sale (checkout confirmation pages).

The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site(s). This can include using a “cookie” which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening, however you will be unable to complete your order online. The information collected in this way can be used to identify your computer activity on our web sites.

Short link: [](http://www.facebook.com/share.php?u=http://name.ly/~FeiR$7) [](http://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=http://name.ly/~FeiR$7) [](mailto:have.a.look@thatis.me?subject=http://name.ly/~FeiR$7) Copy \- <http://name.ly/~FeiR$7>
